<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Have a look at my &lt;span>Portfolio&lt;/span> on Aishwarya Harpale | Portfolio</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/</link><description>Recent content in Have a look at my &lt;span>Portfolio&lt;/span> on Aishwarya Harpale | Portfolio</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 16:48:28 +0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Low Powered Models For Disease Detection</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/low-powered-models/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 20:56:42 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/low-powered-models/</guid><description>Working under LibreHealth organization for Low Powered Models for Disease Detection and Classification for Radiology Images. Experimenting on models such as DenseNet, Inception, etc. Using quantization and pruning techniques to improve model performance in terms of latency, memory usage and power consumption and emulating it on ARM devices using Qemu emulator and Docker.</description></item><item><title>Explainable AI For Healthcare And Finance</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/xai/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:58:10 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/xai/</guid><description>Research in the field of Explainable AI and Interpretable Machine Learning. Identified biases in models trained on healthcare (Breast Cancer Prediction) and financial risk assessment (Home Credit Default Risk Prediction) datasets.</description></item><item><title>Chest-XRay Classification and Localization</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/chest-xray/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:56:43 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/chest-xray/</guid><description>Developed a system for classifying Chest-XRay images into 14 classes using DenseNet, Resnet and VGG. Used localization techniques to draw bounding boxes over the affected sections of images.</description></item><item><title>Plant Disease Detection Using An IoT Device</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/plant-disease/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:55:44 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/plant-disease/</guid><description>Developed a system in collaboration with PICT Affordable Agriculture Lab that could identify diseases in crops using images of leaves. Developed a custom model using CNNs and deployed this model on a Raspberry Pi device for realtime predictions.</description></item><item><title>Book Vendor</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/book-vendor/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/book-vendor/</guid><description>Developed an Android app to sell and purchase second-hand university books from students. Included various features like user authentication, payment module and texting module. App was integrated with Firebase cloud services.</description></item><item><title>Web Portfolio</title><link>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 15:44:46 +0600</pubDate><guid>https://aish-where-ya.github.io/portfolio/portfolio/</guid><description>This Website. Head to my Github for the source code!</description></item></channel></rss>